Guide to the Harry Randall: Fifteenth International Brigade Films and Photographs ALBA.PHOTO.011
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series E: Miscellaneous, 1938-01-1939-09
  - Photo Unit #: E0780 At Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0464)
  - Photo Unit #: E0781 At Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0465)
  - Photo Unit #: E0782 At Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0466)
  - Photo Unit #: E0783 At Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0467)
  - Photo Unit #: E0784 Men returned from USA, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1529)
  - Photo Unit #: E0785 Lincoln-Washington men returning from U.S.A., Jul 1938 (Item 11-0468)
  - Photo Unit #: E0787 [Journalists (?) with typewriter], Jul 1938 (Item 11-0469)
  - Photo Unit #: E0788 Repairing a typewriter, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0470)
  - Photo Unit #: E0789/1 Company 1, Lincoln-Washington, Jun 1938 (Item 11-0381)
  - Photo Unit #: E0789/2 Lincoln-Washington veterans returning to Spain from U.S.A. including Joseph Cobert, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0471)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/47)
  - Photo Unit #: E0790 Repairing a typewriter, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0472)
  - Photo Unit #: E0791 Passing out butts at Lincoln-Washington, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0473)
  - Photo Unit #: E0792 Jack Steele, William Wheeler, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1530)
  - Photo Unit #: E0793 Guard at Lincoln-Washington, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0474)
  - Photo Unit #: E0795 Boxing at Lincoln-Washington, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0475)
  - Photo Unit #: E0796 Boxing at Lincoln-Washington, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0476)
  - Photo Unit #: E0797 Boxing at Lincoln-Washington, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0477)
  - Photo Unit #: E0798 Addressing the 24th battalion, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0478)
  - Photo Unit #: E0805 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion on parade at fiesta, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1833)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/20)
  - Photo Unit #: E0807 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion marching to anniversary fiesta, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1848)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/51)
  - Photo Unit #: E0812 Fiesta, MacKenzie-Papineau, Marca [troops marching with flags], Jul 1938 (Item 11-1531)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/13)
  - Photo Unit #: E0813 MacKenzie-Papineau anniversary fiesta at Marca, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1838)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/31)
  - Photo Unit #: E0816 At MacKenzie-Papineau fiesta, Marca [4 soldiers], Jul 1938 (Item 11-1532)
  - Photo Unit #: E0817 15th International Brigade troops marching [copy negative; transferred from the Victor Berch Papers, ALBA 080], Jun 1938 (Item 1899)
  - Photo Unit #: E0818 Lieutenant Sol Rose [Solomon Rosenblum], MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, undated (Item 11-1844)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/42)
  - Photo Unit #: E0821 Major Edward Cecil Smith, MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, undated (Item 11-1843)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/41)
  - Photo Unit #: E0823 Peasant working in the fields, Marca, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0479)
  - Photo Unit #: E0825 MacKenzie-Papineau celebrates first anniversary at Marca, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1834)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/22)
  - Photo Unit #: E0827 At MacKenzie-Papineau fiesta, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0480)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/12)
  - Photo Unit #: E0829 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion on parade, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1831)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/15)
  - Photo Unit #: E0834 At MacKenzie-Papineau fiesta, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0481)
  - Photo Unit #: E0841 At MacKenzie-Papineau fiesta, Marca; seated 2nd from right Malcolm Dunbar, 3rd from right Jose Antonio Valledor, 4th from right John Gates and [fifth from right?] George Watt, Jul 1, 1938 (Item 11-1533)
  - Photo Unit #: E0843 At MacKenzie-Papineau fiesta, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0482)
  - Photo Unit #: E0846 Activist Congress, Falset [dining-room], Jul 3, 1938 (Item 11-1534)
  - Photo Unit #: E0847 Activist Congress, Falset, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0483)
  - Photo Unit #: E0849 Activist Congress, Falset, Jul 3, 1938 (Item 11-0484)
  - Photo Unit #: E0850 Activist Congress, Falset, Jul 3, 1938 (Item 11-0485)
  - Photo Unit #: E0857 Activist Congress, Falset, Jul 3, 1938 (Item 11-0486)
  - Photo Unit #: E0858 Activist Congress, Falset, Jul 3, 1938 (Item 11-0487)
  - Photo Unit #: E0859 Cubans and girls of Juventud Socialista Unificada at congress, Jul 3, 1938 (Item 11-0488)
  - Photo Unit #: E0861 Cubans at congress, Jul 3, 1938 (Item 11-0489)
  - Photo Unit #: E0865 At Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0490)
  - Photo Unit #: E0866 At Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Jul 3, 1938 (Item 11-0491)
  - Photo Unit #: E0867 At Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Jul 3, 1938 (Item 11-0492)
  - Photo Unit #: E0868 At Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Jul 3, 1938 (Item 11-0493)
  - Photo Unit #: E0869 Presentation of flag by Juventud Socialista Unificada, Jul 3, 1938 (Item 11-0494)
  - Photo Unit #: E0876 Presentation of flag by Juventud Socialista Unificada, Jul 3, 1938 (Item 11-0495)
  - Photo Unit #: E0878 [Group of troops, 3 bare-chested, with tin cups, one African-American], 1938 (Item 11-1535)
  - Photo Unit #: E0880 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, July 4th, Jul 4, 1938 (Item 11-0496)
  - Photo Unit #: E0882 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, July 4th, Jul 4, 1938 (Item 11-0497)
  - Photo Unit #: E0883 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, July 4th, Jul 4, 1938 (Item 11-0498)
  - Photo Unit #: E0891 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, A company marching, Marca, Jun 1938 (Item 11-1536)
  - Photo Unit #: E0892 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, A company marching, Marca, Jun 1938 (Item 11-1537)
  - Photo Unit #: E0893 Group from state of Washington, Jun 1938 (Item 11-0092)
  - Photo Unit #: E0894 Group from State of Washington, Marca, Jun 1938 (Item 11-1538)
  - Photo Unit #: E0895 Group from State of Pennsylvania, Marca, Jun 1938 (Item 11-1539)
  - Photo Unit #: E0896 A Lincoln-Washington Battalion camp, Marca, Jun 1938 (Item 11-1540)
  - Photo Unit #: E0897 A Lincoln-Washington Battalion group (Machine-Gunner Company), Marca, Jun 1938 (Item 11-1541)
  - Photo Unit #: E0898 Lincoln-Washington group (Machine-Gunner Company), Jun 1938 (Item 11-0093)
  - Photo Unit #: E0899 Lincoln-Washington food line (Machine-Gunner Company), Jun 1938 (Item 11-0094)
  - Photo Unit #: E0900 A Lincoln-Washington Battalion food line (Machine-Gunner Company), Marca, Jun 1938 (Item 11-1542)
  - Photo Unit #: E0903 59th Battalion Maneuvers, Jun 1938 (Item 11-0095)
  - Photo Unit #: E0910 15th International Brigade Armory, Marca, Jun 1938 (Item 11-1543)
  - Photo Unit #: E0913 15th International Brigade Armory, Marca, Jun 1938 (Item 11-1544)
  - Photo Unit #: E0915 Sanidad [Health] kitchen, Marca, Jun 1938 (Item 11-1545)
  - Photo Unit #: E0916 MacKenzie-Papineau group, Marca, Jun 1938 (Item 11-1546)
  - Photo Unit #: E0919 15th International Brigade Intendencia, Marca, Jun 1938 (Item 11-1547)
  - Photo Unit #: E0924 Fred Borst cuts Nick Meyers' hair, MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Marca, Jun 1938 (Item 11-1548)
  - Photo Unit #: E0925 MacKenzie-Papineau football team, Jun 1938 (Item 11-1849)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/56)
  - Photo Unit #: E0930 Armory with anti-tank gun. Unloading small anti-tank gun at 15th Armory, Marca, Jun 1938 (Item 11-1549)
  - Photo Unit #: E0932 Armory with anti-tank gun, Jun 1938 (Item 11-1550)
  - Photo Unit #: E0933 Over the top! Lincoln-Washington boys on maneuver, Marca, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1551)
  - Photo Unit #: E0935 Marching feet, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0096)
  - Photo Unit #: E0936 Marching feet, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Marca, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1552)
  - Photo Unit #: E0938 Lincoln-Washington group: [?] Markowitz, Edwin Rolfe, [?] Goldstein, Joe Gordon, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0097)
  - Photo Unit #: E0940 Rolling Auto Park, Marca, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1554)
  - Photo Unit #: E0941 Joe Gordon and Elias Begelman of Williamsburg, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0098)
  - Photo Unit #: E0950 Sighting new travel mortars, Machine-Gunner Company of British Battalion at Marca, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1805)
    (Moscow Number: 5/184/17)
  - Photo Unit #: E0951 Building shelters in British Battalion at Marca, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1803)
    (Moscow Number: 5/184/15)
  - Photo Unit #: E0954 Lincoln-Washington Battalion marching through fields, Marca, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1555)
  - Photo Unit #: E0956-957 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Company 2, light machine-gunner, Marca [copy negative; transferred from the Victor Berch Papers, ALBA 080], Jul 1938 (Item 11-1556)
  - Photo Unit #: E0958 15th International Brigade pagaduris, Marca, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0499)
  - Photo Unit #: E0960 Sanidad [Health] group [in chow line], Marca, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1557)
  - Photo Unit #: E0961 Estado Mayor [Headquarters] "Power Plant," Marca, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0500)
  - Photo Unit #: E0962 Estado Mayor [Headquarters] "Power Plant," Marca, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0501)
  - Photo Unit #: E0963 Edwin Rolfe and James Bourne swimming, Marca, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0502)
  - Photo Unit #: E0965 MacKenzie-Papineau swimming hole, Marca, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0503)
  - Photo Unit #: E0966 Target practice, MacKenzie-Papineau, Marca, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1558)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/58)
  - Photo Unit #: E0968 59th Battalion Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Marca, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1203)
  - Photo Unit #: E0970 Mayor of Marca thanking 15th International Brigade for bread, Jul 17, 1938 (Item 11-0504)
  - Photo Unit #: E0980 Barcelona delegates speak to the 59th Battalion, Jul 17, 1938 (Item 11-0505)
  - Photo Unit #: E0981 Barcelona delegates at 59th Battalion, Jul 17, 1938 (Item 11-0506)
  - Photo Unit #: E0983 15th International Brigade officers and 59th Battalion Officers, Jul 17, 1938 (Item 11-0507)
  - Photo Unit #: E0987 59th Battalion on parade at fiesta, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1827)
  - Photo Unit #: E0991 MacKenzie-Papineau Meeting, a.m. (Item 11-1559)
  - Photo Unit #: E0996 Football game, 35th and 3rd (?) divisions, Jul 17, 1938 (Item 11-1560)
  - Photo Unit #: E0997 Cavalry jumping hurdles, fiesta, Jul 17, 1938 (Item 11-1561)
  - Photo Unit #: E1000 Exercises with rifles, fiesta, Jul 17, 1938 (Item 11-1562)
  - Photo Unit #: E1002 High jump at Lincoln Brigade fiesta, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1563)
  - Photo Unit #: E1004 Jumping hurdles, fiesta, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0508)
  - Photo Unit #: E1006 Jumping hurdles, fiesta, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0509)
  - Photo Unit #: E1010 Activists Conference in Barcelona, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0510)
    (Moscow Number: 5/194/32)
  - Photo Unit #: E1011 Activists Conference in Barcelona [group at dias, man speaking], Jul 1938 (Item 11-1564)
  - Photo Unit #: E1012 Activists Conference in Barcelona [group at dias, man speaking], Jul 1938 (Item 11-1565)
  - Photo Unit #: E1013 Activists Conference in Barcelona [group at dias, man speaking], Jul 1938 (Item 11-1566)
  - Photo Unit #: E1016 Activists Conference in Barcelona, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0511)
  - Photo Unit #: E1018 Activists in Barcelona, Jul 17, 1938 (Item 11-1567)
  - Photo Unit #: E1024 British Battalion fiesta, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1809)
    (Moscow Number: 5/184/22)
  - Photo Unit #: E1025 British Battalion fiesta, Marca, Jul 18, 1938 (Item 11-1804)
    (Moscow Number: 5/184/16)
  - Photo Unit #: E1030 Lieutenant Cipriano Escudero addressing British Battalion at fiesta, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1808)
    (Moscow Number: 5/184/21)
  - Photo Unit #: E1031 British Battalion assembly at fiesta, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1810)
    (Moscow Number: 5/184/23)
  - Photo Unit #: E1035 Football game at British Battalion fiesta, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1807)
    (Moscow Number: 5/184/20)
  - Photo Unit #: E1037 High-jumping competition at British Battalion fiesta, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1811)
    (Moscow Number: 5/184/24)
  - Photo Unit #: E1047 Race in mounting machine guns at British Battalion fiesta, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1812)
    (Moscow Number: 5/184/25)
  - Photo Unit #: E1048 Spanish soldier accidentally wounded at British Battalion fiesta, Marca, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1806)
    (Moscow Number: 5/184/18)
  - Photo Unit #: E1051 Assembly of British Battalion at fiesta, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1813)
    (Moscow Number: 5/184/26)
  - Photo Unit #: E1053 Major Edward Cecil Smith and Commissar Frank Rogers, undated (Item 11-1568)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/54)
  - Photo Unit #: E1054 Lincoln-Washington fiesta, Jul 19, 1938 (Item 11-0099)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/51)
  - Photo Unit #: E1055 Lincoln-Washington Battalion fiesta, Jul 19, 1938 (Item 11-1569)
  - Photo Unit #: E1056 Lincoln-Washington Battalion fiesta, Jul 19, 1938 (Item 11-1570)
  - Photo Unit #: E1057 Lincoln-Washington Battalion fiesta, Jul 19, 1938 (Item 11-1571)
  - Photo Unit #: E1058 Lincoln-Washington Battalion fiesta, boxing match, 2nd anniversary of outbreak of war, Jul 18, 1938 (Item 11-1572)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/46)
  - Photo Unit #: E1059 Lincoln-Washington Battalion fiesta, the winner!, Jul 18, 1938 (Item 11-1573)
  - Photo Unit #: E1060 Lincoln-Washington Battalion fiesta, Mike Pappas [Michael Papadopullo], Jul 18, 1938 (Item 11-1574)
  - Photo Unit #: E1061 Shot-put contest at Lincoln-Washington fiesta, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0100)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/43)
  - Photo Unit #: E1063 Lincoln-Washington Battalion fiesta, Jul 19, 1938 (Item 11-1575)
  - Photo Unit #: E1064 Lincoln-Washington Battalion fiesta, foot race, Jul 19, 1938 (Item 11-1576)
  - Photo Unit #: E1065 Lincoln-Washington Battalion fiesta, three legged race, Jul 19, 1938 (Item 11-1577)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/50)
  - Photo Unit #: E1066 Lincoln-Washington fiesta, Jul 19, 1938 (Item 11-0101)
  - Photo Unit #: E1067 Lincoln-Washington Battalion fiesta, "Virginia item", Jul 19, 1938 (Item 11-1578)
  - Photo Unit #: E1068 Lincoln-Washington Battalion fiesta, Jul 19, 1938 (Item 11-1579)
  - Photo Unit #: E1069 Lincoln-Washington Battalion fiesta, Jul 19, 1938 (Item 11-1580)
  - Photo Unit #: E1070 Lincoln-Washington Battalion fiesta, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1581)
  - Photo Unit #: E1072 Marching to Brigade assembly (Lincoln-Washington Battalion), Jul 19, 1938 (Item 11-1582)
  - Photo Unit #: E1073 Marching to Brigade assembly (Lincoln-Washington Battalion), Jul 19, 1938 (Item 11-1583)
  - Photo Unit #: E1074 Marching to Brigade assembly (Lincoln-Washington Battalion), Jul 19, 1938 (Item 11-1584)
  - Photo Unit #: E1075 Marching to Brigade assembly (Lincoln-Washington Battalion), Jul 19, 1938 (Item 11-1585)
  - Photo Unit #: E1077 Marching to Brigade assembly (Lincoln-Washington Battalion), Jul 19, 1938 (Item 11-1586)
  - Photo Unit #: E1080 15th International Brigade Assembly, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, [marching in ranks], Jul 19, 1938 (Item 11-1785)
    (Moscow Number: 5/181/28)
  - Photo Unit #: E1081 15th International Brigade Assembly, Jul 19, 1938 (Item 11-1587)
    (Moscow Number: 5/181/26)
  - Photo Unit #: E1083 Brigade Assembly, Major José Antonio Valledor speaking, Jul 19, 1938 (Item 11-1588)
  - Photo Unit #: E1084 Brigade Assembly, Major José Antonio Valledor speaking, Jul 19, 1938 (Item 11-1589)
    (Moscow Number: 5/181/25)
  - Photo Unit #: E1085 Brigade Assembly, Major José Antonio Valledor speaking, Jul 19, 1938 (Item 11-1590)
  - Photo Unit #: E1086 15th International Brigade Assembly, 2nd anniversary of outbreak of war, Jul 19, 1938 (Item 11-1591)
  - Photo Unit #: E1087 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Marca, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0512)
  - Photo Unit #: E1089 Lincoln-Washington Battalion building a foxhole, Marca, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1204)
  - Photo Unit #: E1091 Luigi Gallo, John Gates, André Marty, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1592)
  - Photo Unit #: E1092 Chabolas [shelters] at Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Jul 1938 (Item 11-1593)
  - Photo Unit #: E1096 Members of special Machine-Gunner Battalion of 15th army corps, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1594)
  - Photo Unit #: E1100 Town square, Asco, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1595)
  - Photo Unit #: E1102 Fascist prisoners, Asco, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1596)
  - Photo Unit #: E1105 Going to the front lines, Lincoln-Washington, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0102)
  - Photo Unit #: E1107 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Jul 1938 (Item 11-0103)
  - Photo Unit #: E1108 Lincoln-Washington Battalion first-aid post, Corbera, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1597)
  - Photo Unit #: E1109 Lincoln-Washington Battalion first-aid post, Corbera, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1598)
  - Photo Unit #: E1111 Lincoln-Washington Battalion first-aid post, Corbera, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1599)
  - Photo Unit #: E1112 59th Battalion stretcher bearers at Gandesa, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1600)
    (Moscow Number: 5/186/8)
  - Photo Unit #: E1113 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0104)
  - Photo Unit #: E1114 Lincoln-Washington Battalion observer, Corbera, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1601)
  - Photo Unit #: E1115 Lincoln-Washington Battalion observer, Corbera (Item 11-1868)
  - Photo Unit #: E1116 Lincoln-Washington Battalion observer, Corbera, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1602)
  - Photo Unit #: E1117 Lincoln-Washington Battalion Machine-Gunner nest, Corbera, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1603)
  - Photo Unit #: E1118 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1604)
  - Photo Unit #: E1120 Battalion Captain Milton Wolff, Lincoln-Washington, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0105)
  - Photo Unit #: E1121 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Joseph Brandt, Corbera, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1605)
  - Photo Unit #: E1122 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1606)
  - Photo Unit #: E1123 Lincoln-Washington Battalion members resting, Corbera, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1607)
  - Photo Unit #: E1124 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1608)
  - Photo Unit #: E1126 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1609)
  - Photo Unit #: E1127 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1610)
  - Photo Unit #: E1128 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1611)
  - Photo Unit #: E1129 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1612)
  - Photo Unit #: E1130 [Soldiers firing rifles], Jul 1938 (Item 11-1205)
  - Photo Unit #: E1131 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1613)
  - Photo Unit #: E1132 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1614)
  - Photo Unit #: E1133 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1615)
  - Photo Unit #: E1134 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1616)
  - Photo Unit #: E1135 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1617)
  - Photo Unit #: E1136 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1618)
  - Photo Unit #: E1137 Lincoln-Washington Battalion Lieutenant Aaron Lopoff and Lieutenant Rico Rusciano, Corbera, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1619)
  - Photo Unit #: E1138 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1620)
  - Photo Unit #: E1139 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1621)
  - Photo Unit #: E1140 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1622)
  - Photo Unit #: E1141 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera [soldier, from back], undated (Item 11-1623)
  - Photo Unit #: E1142 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1624)
  - Photo Unit #: E1143 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1625)
  - Photo Unit #: E1144 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera [soldier, on ground], Jul 1938 (Item 11-1626)
  - Photo Unit #: E1145 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera [machine gun], Jul 1938 (Item 11-1627)
  - Photo Unit #: E1146 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1628)
  - Photo Unit #: E1147 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1629)
  - Photo Unit #: E1148 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1630)
  - Photo Unit #: E1149 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1631)
  - Photo Unit #: E1150 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1632)
  - Photo Unit #: E1151 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, machine-gun nest, Gandesa [5 soldiers], Jul 1938 (Item 11-1633)
  - Photo Unit #: E1152 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, machine-gun nest, Gandesa, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1634)
  - Photo Unit #: E1153 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, machine-gun nest, Gandesa [4 soldiers], Jul 1938 (Item 11-1635)
  - Photo Unit #: E1154 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, [7 soldiers,] Gandesa, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1636)
  - Photo Unit #: E1155 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, [soldier using] telephone, machine-gun company, Gandesa, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1637)
  - Photo Unit #: E1156 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, [two machine-gunners in trench], undated (Item 11-1638)
  - Photo Unit #: E1157 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, machine-gun company, Gandesa [soldiers at gun], Jul 1938 (Item 11-1639)
  - Photo Unit #: E1158 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, machine-gun company, Gandesa [2 soldiers at gun], Jul 1938 (Item 11-1640)
  - Photo Unit #: E1159 Lincoln-Washington Battalion Estado Mayor, Headquarters of 59th Battalion, 15th International Brigade, during attack on Gandesa, Mark Millman, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1641)
  - Photo Unit #: E1160 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Gandesa [soldiers walking up hill], Jul 1938 (Item 11-1642)
  - Photo Unit #: E1161 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, stretcher bearers, Gandesa, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1643)
  - Photo Unit #: E1162 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Gandesa [soldiers and horses on trail], Jul 1938 (Item 11-1644)
  - Photo Unit #: E1163 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Gandesa [soldiers and horses on trail], Jul 1938 (Item 11-1645)
  - Photo Unit #: E1164 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Gandesa [4 solderis, one with bandaged head, on trail], Jul 1938 (Item 11-1646)
  - Photo Unit #: E1165 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, stretcher bearers, Gandesa, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1647)
  - Photo Unit #: E1166 Lincoln-Washington Battalion stretcher-bearers, Gandesa, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1648)
  - Photo Unit #: E1167 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Gandesa [soldiers relaxing on ground], Jul 1938 (Item 11-1649)
  - Photo Unit #: E1168 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Gandesa [trench?], Jul 1938 (Item 11-1650)
  - Photo Unit #: E1169 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Gandesa, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1651)
  - Photo Unit #: E1170 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Gandesa [soldiers on ground], Jul 1938 (Item 11-1652)
  - Photo Unit #: E1171 Looking toward Corbera [landscape, long view], Jul 1938 (Item 11-1653)
  - Photo Unit #: E1172 Looking toward Gandesa [landscape, long view], Jul 1938 (Item 11-1654)
  - Photo Unit #: E1173 59th Battalion, trench mortar, Gandesa, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1655)
  - Photo Unit #: E1174 59th Battalion, machine-gun nest, Gandesa, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1656)
  - Photo Unit #: E1175 59th Battalion, Gandesa [soldier with rifle, in trench?], Jul 1938 (Item 11-1657)
  - Photo Unit #: E1176 59th Battalion, Gandesa [soldier aiming rifle, behind rocks], Jul 1938 (Item 11-1658)
  - Photo Unit #: E1177 59th Battalion, water detail, Gandesa [two soldiers, with tins], Jul 1938 (Item 11-1659)
  - Photo Unit #: E1178 59th Battalion, water detail, Gandesa [one soldier], Jul 1938 (Item 11-1660)
  - Photo Unit #: E1179 59th Battalion, evacuating wounded, Gandesa [soldier on stretcher], Jul 1938 (Item 11-1661)
  - Photo Unit #: E1180 59th Battalion, evacuating wounded, Gandesa [soldier on stretcher], Jul 1938 (Item 11-1662)
  - Photo Unit #: E1181 15th International Brigade Sanidad [Health] post, Gandesa, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1663)
  - Photo Unit #: E1182 Lincoln-Washington Armory, Gandesa, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1664)
  - Photo Unit #: E1183 15th International Brigade, Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Gandesa [men at tunnle, or bridge, entrance], Aug 1938 (Item 11-1665)
  - Photo Unit #: E1184 Observer, Gandesa, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1666)
  - Photo Unit #: E1185 Planes overhead, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1667)
  - Photo Unit #: E1186 Major José Antonio Valledor and Lieutenant [?] Julia, Gandesa, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1668)
  - Photo Unit #: E1187 Major José Antonio Valledor and Lieutenant Julia, Gandesa, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1669)
  - Photo Unit #: E1188 Captain Dunbar and Major José Antonio Valledor, Gandesa [with 2 others], Aug 1938 (Item 11-1670)